Mertz mss., 1902-2019 LMC 2914
Lilly Library
- Publicity and Appearances
  - Interviews, publicity, and appearance ephemera, 1998 (Box 89, Folder 5)
  - Interviews, publicity, and appearance ephemera, 1999; 2 Folders (Box 89, Folder 6-7)
  - Interviews, publicity, and appearance ephemera, 2000 (Box 89, Folder 8)
  - Interviews, publicity, and appearance ephemera, 2001; 2 Folders (Box 89, Folder 9, Box 192, Folder 8)
  - Interviews, publicity, and appearance ephemera, 2002 (Box 89, Folder 10)
  - Interviews, publicity, and appearance ephemera, 2003 (Box 89, Folder 11)
  - Interviews, publicity, and appearance ephemera, 2004 (Box 89, Folder 12)
  - Interviews, publicity, and appearance ephemera, 2005; 2 Folders (Box 89, Folder 13, Box 192, Folder 9)
  - Interviews, publicity, and appearance ephemera, 2006 (Box 192, Folder 10)
  - Interviews, publicity, and appearance ephemera, 2007-2008 (Box 89, Folder 14)
  - Interviews, publicity, and appearance ephemera, undated; 3 Folders (Box 89, Folder 15-17)
  - Amazon.com interview, 1999 (Box 89, Folder 18)
  - BEA, 2004 (Box 89, Folder 19)
  - Black Orchid/DC ARCE, 1996 (Box 89, Folder 20)
  - Bookstores, undated (Box 89, Folder 21)
  - Boston - ARCE and Audiotour, 2005 (Box 89, Folder 22)
  - Boston Museum and Smithsonian, 2003 (Box 89, Folder 23)
  - Cincinnati, 1996 (Box 89, Folder 24)
  - Denver - 27 Sept. 2004 lecture (Box 90, Folder 1)
  - Egyptian Embassy, 2011 (Box 195, Folder 8)
  - England - Petrie Museum, 2006 (Box 90, Folder 2)
  - Frederick County Public Library, 2001-2002 (Box 90, Folder 3)
  - "Hawkes" bibliography, August 1979 (Box 90, Folder 4)
  - Hershey, 2001-2002 (Box 90, Folder 5)
  - Homewood, 2006 (Box 90, Folder 6)
  - "Interviews/Articles re: Grandmaster", 1998 (Box 90, Folder 7)
  - Johns Hopkins, 2003-2004 (Box 90, Folder 8)
  - "Marketing plan for new Elizabeth Peters book", undated (Box 90, Folder 9)
  - Maryland Author Award, 2012 (Box 192, Folder 12)
  - Memphis, 1996-1997 (Box 90, Folder 10)
  - Michael C. Carlos Museum - Emory University, 2005 (Box 90, Folder 11)
  - Ocean Township - questions from audience, undated (Box 90, Folder 12)
  - Oriental Institute, 1996-1997 (Box 90, Folder 13)
  - PGC with Anne King, 2005-2006 (Box 90, Folder 14)
  - Publicity ideas, 1989-1998 (Box 90, Folder 15)
  - Publication schedules, 1992-1993 (Box 90, Folder 16)
  - "Reasons I Will Not Tour!" - clippings, 2000-2011 (Box 192, Folder 7)
  - Recorded Books interview, 1994 (Box 90, Folder 17)
  - Royal Ontario Museum - SSEA, 1997-1998 (Box 90, Folder 18)
  - "Smithsonian interview - Margaret", 1998-1999 (Box 90, Folder 19)
  - Toledo, 1996 (Box 90, Folder 20)
  - Toledo Museum of Art, 1996 (Box 90, Folder 21)
  - U. Penn Museum, 1996 (Box 90, Folder 22)
  - VA Festival of the Book, 2002 (Box 90, Folder 23)
  - Winterthur, 1997-1998; 2 Folders (Box 90, Folder 24-25)
  - "Women in Ancient Egypt", 1996-1997 (Box 90, Folder 26)
  - Oversize proofs of article about Mertz ("Flowers in the Garden and a New Novel"), 2000 (Box 198)
- Financial and Legal
  - Royalties
    - Agenzia Litteraria Int., 1983-1990 (Box 90, Folder 27)
    - Airplay, 1999-2005 (Box 90, Folder 28)
    - Akcali, 2001-2005 (Box 90, Folder 29)
    - Amazon Publishing, 2017 (Box 90, Folder 30)
    - Armchair Detective Agency, 1991-1994 (Box 90, Folder 31)
    - Atheneum, 1985-1988 (Box 90, Folder 32)
    - Avon Books, 1998-1999 (Box 90, Folder 33)
    - BBC Audiobooks, 1987-2005 (Box 90, Folder 34)
    - Berkley, 1988-1993 (Box 90, Folder 35)
    - Berkley, 1994-1996 (Box 90, Folder 36)
    - Berkley, 1997-1999 (Box 90, Folder 37)
    - Berkley, 2000-2001 (Box 91, Folder 1)
    - Big Apple Agency, 2018 (Box 91, Folder 2)
    - Blackstone, 1995-2007 (Box 91, Folder 3)
    - Blackstone, 2007-2008 (Box 91, Folder 4)
    - Blackstone, 2008 (Box 91, Folder 5)
    - Blackstone, 2008-2011 (Box 91, Folder 6)
    - Blackstone, 2012-2015 (Box 91, Folder 7)
    - Blackstone, 2016-2018 (Box 91, Folder 8)
    - Blackstone, 2018-2019 (Box 91, Folder 9)
    - Bruna Pocketthuis BV, 1983 (Box 91, Folder 10)
    - Campbell, Thompson and McLaughlin Ltd., 1965-1980 (Box 91, Folder 11)
    - Cankarjeva Zalozba, 1985-1986 (Box 91, Folder 12)
    - Casa Editrice Nord (Luigi Bernabo), 1998-2010 (Box 91, Folder 13)
    - Casa, 2010-2012 (Box 91, Folder 14)
    - Casa, 2012-2014 (Box 91, Folder 15)
    - Center Point, 2000-2010 (Box 91, Folder 16)
    - City Editions, 2008-2014 (Box 91, Folder 17)
    - City Editions, 2015 (Box 192, Folder 14)
    - Congdon and Weed, 1983-1989 (Box 91, Folder 18)
    - Contemporary Books, 1989-1991 (Box 91, Folder 19)
    - Coward McCann, 1964-1972 (Box 91, Folder 20)
    - David Grossman (Chivers, Isis, Constable and Robinson, Piathus, Severn, Matt Ashley), 1984-1990 (Box 91, Folder 21)
    - David Grossman (Chivers, Isis, Constable and Robinson, Piathus, Severn, Matt Ashley), 1990-1993 (Box 91, Folder 22)
    - David Grossman (Chivers, Isis, Constable and Robinson, Piathus, Severn, Matt Ashley), 1993-1994 (Box 91, Folder 23)
    - David Grossman (Chivers, Isis, Constable and Robinson, Piathus, Severn, Matt Ashley), 1995-1996 (Box 92, Folder 1)
    - David Grossman (Chivers, Isis, Constable and Robinson, Piathus, Severn, Matt Ashley), 1996-1997 (Box 92, Folder 2)
    - David Grossman (Chivers, Isis, Constable and Robinson, Piathus, Severn, Matt Ashley), 1997-1999 (Box 92, Folder 3)
    - David Grossman (Chivers, Isis, Constable and Robinson, Piathus, Severn, Matt Ashley), 1999-2000 (Box 92, Folder 4)
    - David Grossman (Chivers, Isis, Constable and Robinson, Piathus, Severn, Matt Ashley), 2000-2002 (Box 92, Folder 5)
    - David Grossman (Chivers, Isis, Constable and Robinson, Piathus, Severn, Matt Ashley), 2002-2005 (Box 92, Folder 6)
    - David Grossman (Chivers, Isis, Constable and Robinson, Piathus, Severn, Matt Ashley), 2005-2007 (Box 92, Folder 7)
    - David Grossman (Chivers, Isis, Constable and Robinson, Piathus, Severn, Matt Ashley), 2007-2010 (Box 92, Folder 8)
    - David Grossman (Chivers, Isis, Constable and Robinson, Piathus, Severn, Matt Ashley), 2010-2013 (Box 92, Folder 9)
    - David Grossman (Chivers, Isis, Constable and Robinson, Piathus, Severn, Matt Ashley), 2013-2019 (Box 92, Folder 10)
    - David Grossman (Chivers, Isis, Constable and Robinson, Piathus, Severn, Matt Ashley), 2012 (Box 192, Folder 15)
    - Dodd Mead and Co., 1970-1988 (Box 92, Folder 11)
    - Editions Fleuve Noir, 1971 (Box 92, Folder 12)
    - Encyclopaedia Brittanica, 1998 (Box 92, Folder 13)
    - English Agency (Japan) Ltd., 2001-2009 (Box 92, Folder 14)
    - F. A. Thorpe Ltd., 1984-1986 (Box 92, Folder 15)
    - Fredhois Forlag, 1985 (Box 92, Folder 16)
    - Fredhois Forlag, 1993 (Box 192, Folder 13)
    - Fusosha Ltd., 1990-1998 (Box 92, Folder 17)
    - Gummerus, 1987-1996 (Box 92, Folder 18)
    - Hachette Book Group, 2006-2007 (Box 92, Folder 19)
    - Hachette Book Group, 2007-2009 (Box 92, Folder 20)
    - Hachette Book Group, 2009-2011 (Box 92, Folder 21)
    - Hachette Book Group, 2011-2013 (Box 92, Folder 22)
    - Hachette Book Group, 2013-2015 (Box 92, Folder 23)
    - Hachette Book Group, 2015-2019 (Box 93, Folder 1)
    - Hara Shobo, 2011 (Box 93, Folder 2)
    - HarperCollins, 1994-2000 (Box 93, Folder 3)
    - HarperCollins, 2000-2001 (Box 93, Folder 4)
    - HarperCollins, 2001-2002 (Box 93, Folder 5)
    - HarperCollins, 2002 (Box 93, Folder 6)
    - HarperCollins, 2002-2003 (Box 93, Folder 7)
    - HarperCollins, 2003-2004 (Box 93, Folder 8)
    - HarperCollins, 2004 (Box 93, Folder 9)
    - HarperCollins, 2004-2005 (Box 93, Folder 10)
    - HarperCollins, 2005 (Box 93, Folder 11)
    - HarperCollins, 2005-2006 (Box 93, Folder 12)
    - HarperCollins, 2006; 3 Folders (Box 93, Folder 13-15)
    - HarperCollins, 2006-2007 (Box 93, Folder 16)
    - HarperCollins, 2007; 3 Folders (Box 94, Folder 1-3)
    - HarperCollins, 2007-2008 (Box 94, Folder 4)
    - HarperCollins, 2008; 4 Folders (Box 94, Folder 5-8)
    - HarperCollins, 2008-2009 (Box 94, Folder 9)
    - HarperCollins, 2009; 4 Folders (Box 94, Folder 10-13)
    - HarperCollins, 2009-2010 (Box 94, Folder 14)
    - HarperCollins (folder 1), 2010 (Box 94, Folder 15)
    - HarperCollins (folder 2), 2010 (Box 95, Folder 1)
    - HarperCollins, 2010-2011 (Box 95, Folder 2)
    - HarperCollins, 2011; 2 Folders (Box 95, Folder 3-4)
    - HarperCollins, 2011-2012 (Box 95, Folder 5)
    - HarperCollins, 2012; 2 Folders (Box 95, Folder 6-7)
    - HarperCollins, 2012-2013 (Box 95, Folder 8)
    - HarperCollins, 2013; 2 Folders (Box 95, Folder 9-10)
    - HarperCollins, 2013-2014 (Box 95, Folder 11)
    - HarperCollins, 2014; 2 Folders (Box 95, Folder 12-13)
    - HarperCollins (folder 1), 2015 (Box 95, Folder 14)
    - HarperCollins (folder 2), 2015 (Box 96, Folder 1)
    - HarperCollins, 2015-2016 (Box 96, Folder 2)
    - HarperCollins, 2016 (Box 96, Folder 3)
    - HarperCollins, 2016-2017 (Box 96, Folder 4)
    - HarperCollins, 2017 (Box 96, Folder 5)
    - HarperCollins, 2017-2018 (Box 96, Folder 6)
    - HarperCollins, 2018 (Box 96, Folder 7)
    - HarperCollins, 2018-2019 (Box 96, Folder 8)
    - HarperCollins, 2019 (Box 96, Folder 9)
    - Hawthorn Books, 1970-1972 (Box 96, Folder 10)
    - Heyne Verlag, 1984-1987 (Box 96, Folder 11)
    - J. M. Dent and Sons Ltd., 1969-1972 (Box 96, Folder 12)
    - Lennart Sane/Gotica/Suma de Letras, 1996-2009 (Box 96, Folder 13)
    - Library Livewire Audio, 2000-2001 (Box 96, Folder 14)
    - Lindhardt og Ringhof, 2008-2019 (Box 96, Folder 15)
    - Little, Brown Book Group, 2014-2015 (Box 96, Folder 16)
    - Little, Brown Book Group, 2015-2016 (Box 96, Folder 17)
    - Little, Brown Book Group, 2016-2017 (Box 96, Folder 18)
    - Little, Brown Book Group, 2017-2018 (Box 96, Folder 19)
    - Little, Brown Book Group, 2018-2019 (Box 96, Folder 20)
    - Macmillan, 1986-2018 (Box 97, Folder 1)
    - Marboro/B&N, 1992-1999 (Box 97, Folder 2)
    - Madras Editora, 2006-2009 (Box 97, Folder 3)
    - Margriet, 1985 (Box 97, Folder 4)
    - McGraw-Hill, 2001 (Box 97, Folder 5)
    - Meredith Press, 1966-1969 (Box 97, Folder 6)
    - La Nouvelle Agence, 1992-2005 (Box 97, Folder 7)
    - La Nouvelle Agence, 2005-2015 (Box 97, Folder 8)
    - La Nouvelle Agence, 2015-2019 (Box 97, Folder 9)
    - NTC/Contemporary Publishing Group, 1999-2000 (Box 97, Folder 10)
    - Oy. Weilin and Goos Ab, 1969-1971 (Box 97, Folder 11)
    - P&R, 2013-2018 (Box 97, Folder 12)
    - Pabel Verlag, 1985 (Box 97, Folder 13)
    - Penguin Group (USA), 2002-2005 (Box 97, Folder 14)
    - Peter Bedrick Books, 1990-1998 (Box 97, Folder 15)
    - Phoenix Books, 2009-2019 (Box 97, Folder 16)
    - Les Presses de la Cite, 1969 (Box 97, Folder 17)
    - Reader's Digest, 1992-2008 (Box 97, Folder 18)
    - Recorded Books, 1992-1999 (Box 97, Folder 19)
    - Recorded Books, 1999-2013 (Box 97, Folder 20)
    - Recorded Books, 2014-2019 (Box 97, Folder 21)
    - Remittance advice, 2010-2019 (Box 97, Folder 22)
    - Scherz, 1969-1972 (Box 97, Folder 23)
    - Simon and Schuster, 1988-1994 (Box 97, Folder 24)
    - Simon and Schuster, 1994-1997 (Box 97, Folder 25)
    - Simon and Schuster, 1997-1999 (Box 97, Folder 26)
    - Simon and Schuster, 1999-2002 (Box 97, Folder 27)
    - Simon and Schuster, 2002-2004 (Box 97, Folder 28)
    - Simon and Schuster, 2005-2007 (Box 97, Folder 29)
    - Simon and Schuster, 2008-2011 (Box 97, Folder 30)
    - Simon and Schuster, 2012-2018 (Box 98, Folder 1)
    - Soundelux, 1997-2000 (Box 98, Folder 2)
    - Souvenir Press, 1980-1984 (Box 98, Folder 3)
    - Souvenir Press, 1984-1986 (Box 98, Folder 4)
    - Souvenir Press, 1986-1993 (Box 98, Folder 5)
    - Souvenir Press, 1993-2001 (Box 98, Folder 6)
    - St. Martin's Press, 1987 (Box 98, Folder 7)
    - Tantor, 2007-2019 (Box 98, Folder 8)
    - Tekno Books, 1995-2001 (Box 98, Folder 9)
    - Thomas Schluck, 1987-1994 (Box 98, Folder 10)
    - Thomas Schluck, 1994-1998 (Box 98, Folder 11)
    - Thomas Schluck, 1998-2002 (Box 98, Folder 12)
    - Thomas Schluck, 2002-2005 (Box 98, Folder 13)
    - Thomas Schluck, 2005-2007 (Box 98, Folder 14)
    - Thomas Schluck, 2007-2008 (Box 98, Folder 15)
    - Thomas Schluck, 2008-2010 (Box 98, Folder 16)
    - Thomas Schluck, 2010-2015 (Box 98, Folder 17)
    - Thomas Schluck, 2015-2016 (Box 98, Folder 18)
    - Thomas Schluck, 2017-2019 (Box 98, Folder 19)
    - TOR, 1988-1995 (Box 98, Folder 20)
    - TOR, 1995-1999 (Box 99, Folder 1)
    - TOR, 1999-2002 (Box 99, Folder 2)
    - TOR, 2003-2007 (Box 99, Folder 3)
    - Uitgeverig de Fontein, 1967-1970 (Box 99, Folder 4)
    - Warner Books, 1985-1998 (Box 99, Folder 5)
    - Warner Books, 1998-2001 (Box 99, Folder 6)
    - Warner Books, 2001-2004 (Box 99, Folder 7)
    - Warner Books, 2004-2019 (Box 99, Folder 8)
    - Washington Post, 1984-1985 (Box 99, Folder 9)
    - Weilen & Goos, 1983-1988 (Box 99, Folder 10)
    - The Writer, 1994 (Box 99, Folder 11)
    - Miscellaneous royalties, 1983-2011 (Box 99, Folder 12)
  - Bank of America, 2006-2008; 5 Folders (Box 99, Folder 13-17)
  - Business receipts (folders 1-4), 2006-2010; 4 Folders (Box 99, Folder 18-21)
  - Business receipts (folders 5-7), 2006-2010; 3 Folders (Box 100, Folder 1-3)
  - Car, 2006-2010 (Box 100, Folder 4)
  - Character/reproduction rights, 2011 (Box 100, Folder 5)
  - Charlotte MacLeod, 1999-2003 (Box 100, Folder 6)
  - Contributions, 2006-2010; 6 Folders (Box 100, Folder 7-12)
  - Copyright, 1978-2012; 2 Folders (Box 100, Folder 13-14)
  - Credit card statements (folders 1-4), 2005-2010; 4 Folders (Box 100, Folder 15-18)
  - Credit card statements (folders 5-8), 2005-2010; 4 Folders (Box 101, Folder 1-4)
  - Earned income, 1987-2010; 6 Folders (Box 101, Folder 5-10)
  - Earthwood, 2007 (Box 101, Folder 11)
  - Estate of Earl D. Gross, 1978-1980; 5 Folders (Box 101, Folder 12-16)
  - Farmers and Mechanics National Bank (folders 1-2), 1983; 2 Folders (Box 101, Folder 17-18)
  - Farmers and Mechanics National Bank (folders 3-4), 1983; 2 Folders (Box 102, Folder 1-2)
  - Farmers and Mechanics National Bank, 1984; 5 Folders (Box 102, Folder 3-7)
  - Farmers and Mechanics National Bank, 1986; 4 Folders (Box 102, Folder 8-11)
  - Farmers and Mechanics National Bank, 1987 (Box 102, Folder 12)
  - Farmers and Mechanics National Bank, 1988; 4 Folders (Box 102, Folder 13-16)
  - Farmers and Mechanics National Bank (folder 1), 1989 (Box 102, Folder 17)
  - Farmers and Mechanics National Bank (folders 2-5), 1989; 4 Folders (Box 103, Folder 1-4)
  - Farmers and Mechanics National Bank, 1990; 5 Folders (Box 103, Folder 5-9)
  - Farmers and Mechanics National Bank, 1991; 5 Folders (Box 103, Folder 10-14)
  - Farmers and Mechanics National Bank, 2006; 2 Folders (Box 103, Folder 15-16)
  - Farmers and Mechanics National Bank, 2007; 2 Folders (Box 104, Folder 1-2)
  - First National Bank of Maryland, 1983-1990; 2 Folders (Box 104, Folder 3-4)
  - ING, 2010 (Box 104, Folder 5)
  - Income ledger, 1986-2006 (Box 104, Folder 6)
  - Lambrose land sale, 2007 (Box 104, Folder 7)
  - Landscaping and garden, 1988-1992; 4 Folders (Box 104, Folder 8-11)
  - Maryland National Bank, 1983-1988; 2 Folders (Box 104, Folder 12-13)
  - Merrill Lynch, 1982-1987; 2 Folders (Box 104, Folder 14-15)
  - Office equipment, 2005-2009 (Box 104, Folder 16)
  - PNC (folders 1-3), 2006-2010; 3 Folders (Box 104, Folder 17-19)
  - PNC (folder 4), 2006-2010 (Box 105, Folder 1)
  - Postage, 2006-2010; 4 Folders (Box 105, Folder 2-5)
  - Receipts and personal expenses, 1976-1979; 4 Folders (Box 105, Folder 6-9)
  - Receipts and personal expenses (folders 1-8), 1980-1989; 8 Folders (Box 105, Folder 10-17)
  - Receipts and personal expenses (folder 9), 1980-1989 (Box 106, Folder 1)
  - Receipts and personal expenses, 1990-1999; 7 Folders (Box 106, Folder 2-8)
  - Receipts and personal expenses (folders 1-9), 2000-2009; 9 Folders (Box 106, Folder 9-17)
  - Receipts and personal expenses (folders 10-12), 2000-2009; 3 Folders (Box 107, Folder 1-3)
  - Sales and reprint figures, 1992-2017 (Box 107, Folder 4)
  - Travel and entertainment, 1990-2009; 11 Folders (Box 107, Folder 5-15)
  - Travel and entertainment, 1993-2012; 6 Folders (Box 192, Folders 16-21)
  - Utilities (folder 1), 2006-2010 (Box 107, Folder 16)
  - Utilities (folders 2-9), 2006-2010; 8 Folders (Box 108, Folder 1-8)
  - Vet, 2008-2010 (Box 108, Folder 9)
  - Contracts
    - AMSCO School Productions, 1998 (Box 108, Folder 10)
    - AW Bruna and Zoons, 1978 (Box 108, Folder 11)
    - Airplay, 1997 (Box 108, Folder 12)
    - Albatros, 2000 (Box 108, Folder 13)
    - Alfa, 1993 (Box 108, Folder 14)
    - Alpress, 1998-2004 (Box 108, Folder 15)
    - Amarna Productions, 2008 (Box 108, Folder 16)
    - American Audio Literature, 2001 (Box 108, Folder 17)
    - Anhui Literature, 2000 (Box 108, Folder 18)
    - Armchair Detective Agency, 1990 (Box 108, Folder 19)
    - Arnoldo Mondatori Editore, 1997-2002 (Box 108, Folder 20)
    - Ast, 1996 (Box 108, Folder 21)
    - Atheneum, 1986-1987 (Box 108, Folder 22)
    - Avon, 1997-1999 (Box 108, Folder 23)
    - BBC Audiobooks America, 2006 (Box 108, Folder 24)
    - Berkley, 1985-2006 (Box 108, Folder 25)
    - Biuarupa Aksara, 1993-1994 (Box 108, Folder 26)
    - Blackstone, 1997-2011 (Box 108, Folder 27)
    - Bolinda, 2000 (Box 108, Folder 28)
    - Bruna Pockethuis, 1981-1982 (Box 108, Folder 29)
    - Caralt, 1969 (Box 108, Folder 30)
    - Casa Editrice Sonzogno, 1974 (Box 108, Folder 31)
    - Casa Editrice Nord, 2004-2010 (Box 108, Folder 32)
    - Cassell and Co., 1974-1977 (Box 108, Folder 33)
    - Cengage Learning, 2008 (Box 108, Folder 34)
    - Center Point, 2000-2006 (Box 108, Folder 35)
    - Chivers Press, 1991-2000 (Box 108, Folder 36)
    - City Editions, 2007-2011 (Box 108, Folder 37)
    - Clio Press, 1992-1993 (Box 108, Folder 38)
    - Compendium contracts, 2000-2003 (Box 108, Folder 39)
    - Congdon and Weed, 1984 (Box 108, Folder 40)
    - Constable-Robinson, 1999-2009 (Box 109, Folder 1)
    - Coronet Books, 1974 (Box 109, Folder 2)
    - Cosmopolitan, 1982 (Box 109, Folder 3)
    - Coward-McCann, 1962-1966 (Box 109, Folder 4)
    - Crippen and Landru, 2002 (Box 109, Folder 5)
    - Cron Press, 1997 (Box 109, Folder 6)
    - Curley Publishing, 1990-1992 (Box 109, Folder 7)
    - Daw Books, 1998 (Box 109, Folder 8)
    - Djar, 2002 (Box 109, Folder 9)
    - Dodd Mead and Co., 1970-1981? (Box 109, Folder 10)
    - Dominick Abel, 2003 (Box 109, Folder 11)
    - Donald I. Fine, 1992 (Box 109, Folder 12)
    - Dove Entertainment, 1998 (Box 109, Folder 13)
    - Econ Verlag, 1993-2001 (Box 109, Folder 14)
    - Editions du Fleuve Noir, 1969-1971 (Box 109, Folder 15)
    - Editions Jean-Claude Lattes, 1974 (Box 109, Folder 16)
    - Editions Mondiales, 1975-1978 (Box 109, Folder 17)
    - Editions Olivier Orban, 1991 (Box 109, Folder 18)
    - Editora Madras, 2003 (Box 109, Folder 19)
    - Editorial Suma, 2006 (Box 109, Folder 20)
    - Enalios, 2001-2002 (Box 109, Folder 21)
    - The English Agency (Japan), 2001-2003 (Box 109, Folder 22)
    - Epsilon Yayincilik, 2009-2012 (Box 109, Folder 23)
    - F. A. Thorpe Ltd., 1979-1993 (Box 109, Folder 24)
    - Fawcett, 1972-1981 (Box 109, Folder 25)
    - Femmes d'Aujourd'hui, 1968 (Box 109, Folder 26)
    - Finnish Broadcasting Company, 1995 (Box 109, Folder 27)
    - Fredhois Forlag, 1974-1993 (Box 109, Folder 28)
    - Fusosha Ltd., 1991 (Box 109, Folder 29)
    - G. K. Hall, 1975-1990 (Box 109, Folder 30)
    - Galef Institute, 1997 (Box 109, Folder 31)
    - Generights, 2006-2011 (Box 109, Folder 32)
    - Gotica, 2002-2006 (Box 109, Folder 33)
    - Greenhaven Press, 2000 (Box 109, Folder 34)
    - "Guide to the Authors Guild Trade Book Contract", 1972 (Box 109, Folder 35)
    - Gummerus, 1992-1994 (Box 109, Folder 36)
    - Hara Shobo, 2010 (Box 109, Folder 37)
    - HarperCollins, 1993-2012; 3 Folders (Box 109, Folder 38-40)
    - Hawthorn Books, 1973 (Box 109, Folder 41)
    - Herbert Jenkins Ltd., 1967-1968 (Box 109, Folder 42)
    - Hodder and Stroughton, 1966 (Box 109, Folder 43)
    - Hodder Fawcett, 1970 (Box 109, Folder 44)
    - Hsin Chao She, 1991 (Box 109, Folder 45)
    - Iljus, 1996 (Box 109, Folder 46)
    - Illustris Forlag, 1993 (Box 109, Folder 47)
    - Industrie Grafiche Cine del Duca, 1967-1981 (Box 109, Folder 48)
    - Isis, 1994-2004 (Box 109, Folder 49)
    - J. M. Dent and Sons Ltd., 1968 (Box 109, Folder 50)
    - Javier Vergara, 1993-1995 (Box 109, Folder 51)
    - Konrad Theiss Verlag, 2010 (Box 109, Folder 52)
    - Lasabra, 1981 (Box 109, Folder 53)
    - Librairie Generale Francaise/Livre de Poche, 1997-2006 (Box 109, Folder 54)
    - Marboro, 1991-1992 (Box 109, Folder 55)
    - Mars Konyvkiado, 1993 (Box 109, Folder 56)
    - Medialiuros, 2007 (Box 109, Folder 57)
    - Medias Ohg Verlag, 2013 (Box 109, Folder 58)
    - Meredith Press, 1965-1968 (Box 109, Folder 59)
    - Mike Ashley, 1993-2002 (Box 109, Folder 60)
    - Mono and Manana, 2006 (Box 109, Folder 61)
    - Mortensen Magazine Group, 1978 (Box 109, Folder 62)
    - Mystery Writers of America, 1995-1996 (Box 109, Folder 63)
    - Nakladatelstvi Domino, 2008 (Box 109, Folder 64)
    - Nakladnik, 2005 (Box 109, Folder 65)
    - National Center for Translation, 2009 (Box 109, Folder 66)
    - Nelson Doubleday, 1978 (Box 109, Folder 67)
    - Newfront Productions, 1998 (Box 109, Folder 68)
    - NewStar Media, 1998 (Box 109, Folder 69)
    - Oakhill Publishing, 2009 (Box 109, Folder 70)
    - Oglak Yayinlari, 2000 (Box 109, Folder 71)
    - The One Publishing, 2005 (Box 109, Folder 72)
    - Oxford University Press, 1993 (Box 109, Folder 73)
    - Peter Bedrick Books, 1989 (Box 109, Folder 74)
    - Phantom Press, 1998-2002 (Box 109, Folder 75)
    - Phoenix Books, 2009 (Box 109, Folder 76)
    - Piatkus, 1986-1993 (Box 109, Folder 77)
    - Planeta Editora, 1995-1999 (Box 109, Folder 78)
    - Prava I Prevodi, 2006-2009 (Box 109, Folder 79)
    - Presses de la Cite, 1967-1971 (Box 109, Folder 80)
    - Proszynski, 1998-1999 (Box 109, Folder 81)
    - Prozoretz, 2006 (Box 109, Folder 82)
    - R.A.O., 2007 (Box 109, Folder 83)
    - Reader's Digest, 1969-2009 (Box 109, Folder 84)
    - Recorded Books (folder 1), 1991-2006 (Box 109, Folder 85)
    - Recorded Books (folders 2-4), 1991-2006; 3 Folders (Box 110, Folder 1-3)
    - "Reversions", 1988-2010 (Box 110, Folder 4)
    - Robinson, 2002 (Box 110, Folder 5)
    - Scherz Verlag, 1969-1992 (Box 110, Folder 6)
    - Schneekluth Verlag, 1991-1992 (Box 110, Folder 7)
    - Severn House, 1989-1995 (Box 110, Folder 8)
    - Simon and Schuster, 1991-1998 (Box 110, Folder 9)
    - Sophisticated Traveler (NYT), 1995 (Box 110, Folder 10)
    - Soundelux, 1995 (Box 110, Folder 11)
    - Souvenir Press, 1975-1981 (Box 110, Folder 12)
    - Sovershenno Secretno, 1994-1995 (Box 110, Folder 13)
    - Suma de Letras, 2002-2005 (Box 110, Folder 14)
    - Sweetwater, 2001-2002 (Box 110, Folder 15)
    - Tantor Media, 2007-2008 (Box 110, Folder 16)
    - Thorndike Press, 1989 (Box 110, Folder 17)
    - TOR, 1986-1993 (Box 110, Folder 18)
    - U. Mursia and C. Editore, 1969 (Box 110, Folder 19)
    - Uitgeverig de Fontein, 1966 (Box 110, Folder 20)
    - Ullstein Verlag, 2002-2011 (Box 110, Folder 21)
    - Verlagsgruppe Weltbilel, 2003-2009 (Box 110, Folder 22)
    - Victor Gollancz, 1963 (Box 110, Folder 23)
    - "Visual medium", 1970-2008 (Box 110, Folder 24)
    - Walter J. Black, 1973-1981 (Box 110, Folder 25)
    - Warner Books, 1999-2010 (Box 110, Folder 26)
    - Washington Post, 2001 (Box 110, Folder 27)
    - Weilen & Goos, 1966-1973 (Box 110, Folder 28)
    - Wilhelm Heyne Verlag, 1970-1994 (Box 110, Folder 29)
  - Royalties journals, undated; 2 Folders (Box 110, Folder 30-31)
  - Financial daybooks, 1976-1979; 2 Folders (Box 110, Folder 32-33)
  - Miscellaneous financial and legal, 1990-2012; 4 Folders (Box 111, Folder 1-4)
- Subject Files